

JAYALAKSHMI PASURLA

Stockholm · +46727859919 jayalakshmipasurla@gmail.com | LinkedIn

A software engineer who recently worked as Intern at FCG Global and was a Software Engineer working on ServiceNow after embarking on a learning journey of ServiceNow platform with H&M Group as an Upskill consultant where I successfully completed the certification as Certified System Administrator (CSA) for ServiceNow.

I am a fast learner, good at multi-tasking, and working efficiently, quickly solving any problems that may arise. I am a goal-oriented person, striving to constantly develop and challenge myself. I believe I will be an excellent addition to your team, contributing with my positivity and eagerness to learn.

EXPERIENCE

FEB 2023-AUG 2023

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN, FCG GLOBAL

Working in FCG GLOBAL as Tech expert in an Innovation team where my job is to find and solve the problems in the organization and for FCG's clients in an innovative way using tech i.e., using low code tools like Microsoft PowerApps, Microsoft Power BI etc.,

MARCH 2022 - JULY 2022

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, THE UPSKILL COMPANY (CONSULTANT AT H&M GROUP)

Started the journey as part of an accelerated learning program and was later induced into a product team as software engineer. I was actively part of a team which focused on ITSM, Dashboards, Configuration, and Integrations. Have attained clear working knowledge on agile technologies and business tech way of working in H&M Group. Maintained clear communications on requirements with product owner and delivered as per the expectation.

JULY 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2020

ASSOCIATE, WIPRO LIMITED

Experienced in gathering, documenting and analyzing business requirements and solving them using pega. Knowledge on pega implementation cycles including development testing and implementation. Exposure in SDLC lifecycle. Involved in development of Data Model, Process Flows, Activities, Activity Step Methods and User Interface.

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

BACHELOR OF TECH IN ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING, RGM COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY, INDIA

Most of my course work is concerned with the study, design, and application of equipment, devices, and systems which use electricity, electronics, and electromagnetism. Learned to independently identify, formulate, and solve problems and carry out tasks within the given time frames. I was an active member of the cultural club and was part of organizing committees which helped me to attain leadership skills and teamwork.

This experience allowed me to develop valuable skills such as Electricity electronics and electromagnetism, Leadership skills, and Teamwork.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

- Free Energy generation using DC machines.
- Fully automated solar grass cutter.
- Design of Smart based water grid system.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ServiceNow Power BI
- CMDBPega
- ITSM
 HTML and CSS
- Integrations
 JavaScript

SOFT SKILLS

- Analytical Thinking
- Agile Methods
- Problem Solving
- Organization Skills
- Service Minded
- Creativity
- Efficiency
- Responsibility
- Sustainable Thinking

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified System Administrator (CSA), Service Now
- Pega System Architect Certification (PCSA)74V1

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Participated in Smart India Hackathon 2018 and achieved AICTE Encouragement Award.
- Highest number of appreciations received in project for record number of closures.